uh how many Christians are out here
today raise your hand if you're a
Christian amen um what is what are the
two greatest Commandments for the
Christian commandment number one what
love the Lord your God with all your
heart commandment number
two love your neighbor as yourself so
how many of you realize it is your
Christian duty to love
me
you understand that right you love me no
matter what right yall
like um we're going to talk today uh
we're going to get into the word of God
today
amen and um we are going to um we're
going to visit some uncomfortable
topics but things that need to be said
so I'm G ask you one more time how many
of you love me
I I love you too I love you too and I
want y'all to know something right and
I'm going to getting getting ready to
pray but I want you to know something um
when I left my career as a hip-hop
artist and joined this church um it was
the best decision I ever made in my
life and I am jealous of
you y' y'all caught what I just said
I am jealous of
you because you are God's
church and I'm jealous over God's church
I don't want anybody touching God's
Church y'all y'all with me and so when I
see a
danger that threatens God's church it's
my responsibility to speak are y'all
with me do you love me let's pray
heavenly father bless us Lord
as we open your word in Jesus name we
pray amen so uncomfortable topic number
one the march on the
capital the march on the capital I want
you to understand that the march on the
capital and Christian nationalism are
are definitely
intertwined do y'all understand what I'm
saying it is definitely intertwined now
some of you have already gotten quiet
after I asked if you love me you're
already like oh you already started out
wrong but I want you to understand
something beloved that the march on the
capital Did you know that the B listen
let's just go there we're going to talk
about the march on the capital
Revelation chapter 20 Revelation chapter
20 uh and we're going to begin with
verse 7 Revelation 20 and verse
7 and you are
not there we go the Bible says and when
the thousand years were expired
Satan shall be loosed out of his prison
and shall go out to deceive the Nations
which are in the four quarters of the
earth Gog and MOG to gather them to the
battle the number of whom is as the sand
of the sea and they went upon a breath
of the earth and marched on the
capital they marched on the
capital now I don't know about you but I
don't want to be in that march on the
capital
how many of you want to be in that march
on the capital because the people that
are in this march on the capital believe
that Satan is the rightful pres
leader the rightful
leader a and and Satan has duped the
people into believing that he is the
rightful
King and listen to me there is nothing
that can be said to the people at this
time that will change their mind they
believe that he is the rightful
ruler no matter how much we no matter
how much pleading at this time probation
is closed long Clos it's the end of the
1,000 years and the people believe that
the kingdom has been stolen from
him that that the inauguration of Christ
was
rigged
and so so the the here is the scary
thing about this y'all is that in this
group there will be seventh day
Adventists that's a sobering
thought how in the world could
Adventists who knew better who
understood the gospel how in the world
can Adventist be a part of this group at
the end of
time at the end of the millennial
the Bible describes a second group it
describes a second group in Revelation
20:4 and I saw Thrones and they sat upon
them and judgment was given unto them
and I saw the souls of them that were
beheaded for the witness of Jesus and
for the word of God and which had not
worshiped the Beast neither his image
neither had received his Mark upon their
foreheads or in their hands and they
lived and reigned with Christ how long a
thousand years so there were two groups
here one that lived and reigns with
Christ for a thousand years and another
group who believes that the kingdom has
been wrongly stolen from its rightful
leader and they are involved in the
March upon the
capital New
Jerusalem I know what y'all thought I
was talking about which is why y'all are
like but I'm just talking about the
march on the
capital that's
all so the question is how do do we be a
part of the how can we be a part of this
it first the the group that that lives
and reign with Christ versus being a
part of that other group that were
Marchers on they're
riers they're going to Riot to try to
take the kingdom of God and the answer
is going to shock you how many of you
want to be a part of that first group
the part that lives and reigns with
Christ for a thousand years well you
have to become
something you have to become a Christian
nationalist what I'm about to say is
going to shock you but I want you to
know that I am a Christian
[Laughter]
nationalist Pastor what are you doing up
there
I I am a
Christian
nationalist allow me to break it down
for you you see when we go to the Book
of Revelation chapter 4 the Bible says
after this I looked and behold a door
was opened in heaven and the first voice
which I heard was as it were a trumpet
talking with me which said come up
hither and I will show unto the things
which must be
Hereafter John is taken up into a
Heavenly City into the Heavenly
Jerusalem what the Bible calls a better
country a better
Nation how many of you would like to be
a part of the nation of Heaven yeah so
to be a part of the nation of heaven you
must
become Christian nationalist I can say
it proudly I am a Christian nationalist
maybe not in the way that some of you
think when you first heard me say that
but I am a Christian
Nationalist and my appeal is for you all
to
become Christian
nationalists y'all are really struggling
right
now like but I
thought John in in describing this
Vision that he sees in heaven the Bible
says in verse two immediately I was in
the spirit and behold a throne was set
in heaven and one sat on the throne ver
vers three and he that sat on the throne
was to look upon like a Jasper and a
sarden stone and there was a rainbow
round about the throne in sight like
unto an emerald now I want you to watch
Watch What Happens Next in verse six of
chapter 5 John says I beheld and lo in
the midst of the throne and of the four
beast and in the midst of the elders
stood a what a lamb as it had been slain
having seven horns and seven eyes which
are the seven spirits of God sent into
all the Earth I'm going to come back to
this in a moment so I'm going to ask you
a
question all the angels and all the
beings in heaven worship this
lamb what animal would you use to the
answer is already there to describe this
heavenly
Nation the lamb the lamb is the symbol
of this heavenly Nation a lamb as it had
been what slain
so our Nation
Beloved the country that we are citizens
of when we are born again is the country
of
Heaven God calls us to be good citizens
of this country and you'll remember that
Jesus put it this way Jesus answered and
said my kingdom is what not of this
world if my kingdom were of this world
then would my servants fight that I
should not be delivered to the Jews but
now is my kingdom not from hence so if
Jesus's kingdom is not of this world
then our kingdom is not of this world
I'm a citizen I'm a nationalist but I'm
a Christian Nationalist and being a true
Christian nationalist does not mean I
love America it means I love the Kingdom
of
Heaven it doesn't mean I love Jamaica it
doesn't mean I love fil the blank of
whatever Nation you want it and listen
there's nothing wrong with loving your
country but when you put love of country
this country above love of that
country now we have a
problem now we have a problem so God
says listen I want you to be citizens of
the Kingdom of Heaven I want you to be
nationalists so what is a nationalist a
nationalist is one who does every he
loves his his country she loves her
country and they will do
anything to promote the mission and the
values of that
country so what does it mean in a
practical sense to be a Christian
nationalist well this is the this is the
mission of the Christian
nationalist there it is right there
y'all Revelation 14:6 I saw another
angel fly in the midst of Heaven having
the Everlasting gospel to preach unto
them that dwell on the earth and to
Every Nation Kindred tongue and people
saying with a loud voice fear God and
give glory to him for the hour of his
judgment is come and worship him that
made Heaven the Earth the sea and The
Fountains of waters the the mission of
the Heavenly
nation is to go into all Earthly
Nations and preach the
truth fear God is the message let me ask
you a question if there was a nation on
Earth that was fearing God would the
gospel go to Every Nation or would some
Nations be left
out it the reason it's going to every
nation is because no Nation on
Earth did y'all catch me no Nation on
Earth fears
God that's why the message is to go to
Every Nation Kindred tongue and
people now I want you to see something
else because uh uh the Bible tells us in
Matthew chapter 9:1 17 the Bible says
here uh neither Jesus speaking says
neither do men put new wine into all
bottles else the bottles break and the
wine run it out but the bottle and the
bottle perisheth but they put new wine
into what new bottles and both are
preserved so let me ask you a question
what is new wine according to this this
verse what do you think new wine
symbolizes say again Doctrine the
gospel isn't that good news y'all we're
supposed to be going to the world
presenting them with
wine where're supposed to be presenting
them with wine what is that wine we saw
it in the Three Angels messages first
angel fear God and give glory to him
this is part of the
wine are y'all following this is part of
the wine that that that as Christian
nationalists we're supposed to be taken
into the world fear God and keep his
Commandments part of that wine hey
there's this power
called
Babylon that is
offering counterfeit
wine
and number three the third Angel's
message is a prophetic understanding
right of of of of the end time events
how they unfold so that third second
Angel's message they following another
Angel saying Babylon has fallen has
fallen that great City because she made
all nations drink of the what the wine
of the wrath of her
fornication God calls us to call people
out of Babylon and we
read from the great controversy page 388
this cup of intoxication which he
presents to the world represents the
false doctrines that she has accepted as
a result of her unlawful connection with
the great ones of the earth friendship
with the world corrupts her faith and in
turn and in her turn she exerts a
corrupting influence on the World by
teaching doctrines which are opposed to
the plainest statements of holy RIT or
of holy
scriptures but then the third angel
message follows a message that we see is
a prophetic warning about end time
events that would lead to the fall of
the enemies of God's people and the
final exaltation of the nation of
Heaven why is it
significant what is my warning here for
Adventists
today I want you to understand
that that there is something else in the
Bible it's found in Revelation
13:1 that picks up on this very same
description the Bible says here and I
beheld another Beast coming up out of
the what Earth he had horns like a
lamb
and he would eventually speak like a
dragon
amen not amen why are you not amening me
he had horns like a lamb and sometime in
the
future he would speak like a
[Music]
dragon no no no no no no no he had horns
like a lamb and he what he spake as a
dragon signifying that whatever power
this is yes it is going to do worse
things in the future but from its very
Inception
please how many of you love
me just checking I got to check
periodically from its Inception it
speaks as a dragon the dragon voice will
get louder as we get closer to the end
of time but it has been hypocritical
from its
Inception now please understand me
hypocritical doesn't mean that that
we're not you know how we talk about
when we say the papacy we're not talking
about peoples we're talking about
systems you know we say that yeah I want
you to understand that that the nation
that is being described here is a nation
that is that is a mixed
bag there was much
good amen and there was much
hypocrisy it's like in some phases it
was lambik and in another phases dragon
likee is that is that a good
balance so so so notice though notice
though here's where we get thrown off
number one we think oh this is going to
happen sometime in the future no it it's
happened from its
Inception and and when we understand
that it's happened from its Inception
what I find is a lot of people are for
some reason like I got a you know the
first Beast of Bible prophecy yay you
know the SEC we got to protect that
lamb don't talk against the
lamb but when the pope sneezes ha I knew
I knew that sneeze meant
something I'm telling you Sunday law is
right around the corner you saw the way
when you saw you saw his eye
right y'all sleeping y'all sleeping and
so we do that we we we we put this
emphasis on the first beast and we even
put emphasis on that Beast from the
abyss in Revelation 11 but for some
reason and I let me
not for some
reason
Adventists are protective of this second
beast don't touch the
Beast don't speak against the beast but
what I need you to understand because I
know what you're thinking already this
Beast represents
America yes and no
because to say that it represents
America is really a broad statement
there is something more specific that it
represents within
America and when we can differentiate
between between the the nation and then
what it represents within America then
we can sit back and breathe a little bit
Ah okay not so listen listen listen
listen to what we're told here next he
sees a beast uh with two horns like a
lamb but he's fake as a dragon this we
believe means the United States the
government is lamb likee in appearance
but dragon likee in action it's
profession it it's in profession it is
the land of liberty but in action it is
the land
of slavery and
oppression so if I were to ask you test
question did this lamb speak as a dragon
from its Inception the answer would
be
and now notice
this Ellen White says the churches
represented by Babylon are represented H
as having fallen from their spiritual
state to become a persecuting power
against those who keep the Commandments
of God and have the testimony of Jesus
now listen to
this to John this persecuting power is
represented as
having horns like a
lamb but speaking as a dragon who is she
identifying as this two-horned Beast
here churches
churches in
America and now we can begin to
understand why there's a distinction yes
generally speaking the the nation is
America but more specifically speaking
we're talking about Fallen churches
apostate protestantism within
America and now when you understand that
it might be a little bit more easy for
you to say yes it's spoken like that
from its
Inception when it comes upon the scene
it is already this the same people who
left other lands to establish religious
liberty here did not afford it to
others are y'all with me so
far so so then these Fallen churches are
are what is more specifically
represented as the Beast having horns of
a lamb and speaking like a dragon
meaning that this Beast is now going or
this this Fallen Babylon representing
the churches are going forth with
false
doctrines now I need y'all to understand
something
because as Adventists we limit the wine
to
Doctrine and and so when I say Doctrine
throw some things out to me when I say
Doctrine what do you think of Sabbath
right what
else state of the dead right what
else the the health message right the
sanctuary we think Doctrine and and and
and and what we don't
understand is
that you can reject the doctrines of
Babylon and yet still be drinking her
wine
because you see part of her teachings
has to do with the way that she
interprets actions in the
world her
philosophy the way that she looks at
prophecy and prophetic
events and Beloved the reason that it is
so important to understand this is
because all three of these messages are
counterfeited by
Babylon so just as the first Angel's
message is a call to keep the
Commandments of God the babylon's first
message
is the law of God doesn't stand or if it
does you we ought to be keeping the
first day of the
week that's a counterfeit of the first
Angel's message there is also a
counterfeit of the second Angel's
message are you'all ready for this
counterfeit in the second Angel's
message we understand that Babylon
represents
the come on y'all it represents the
Fallen churches that is the enemy that
is who God says keep your eye on that is
the end time adversary but in in
apostate babylon's of verse an apostate
Protestants version of the second
Angel's message guess who the enemies
are the
atheists the secular the
marxists those
Communists the people that want to get
rid of our
religion and beloved I need y'all to
understand
something if you start drinking
that I should just end the I should just
the presentation right here I just end
if you see you might not be drinking hey
Sunday is the real Sabbath that tastes
CRA
no no Adventist is going to drink
that they're not going to drink when you
die you go straight to heaven now I
don't want that drink would you like a
drink no thank you I don't
drink that's good we should not drink is
drinking wine is drinking alcohol a sin
for us according to the
Bible oh w
I got to change the
subject is drinking alcohol prohibited
in the
Bible
yes
yeah oh man y'all going to make me
change subjects
Midstream maybe maybe that's the
problem maybe we think it's okay to
drink a little mixed wine every now and
then in Temperance you know
be tempered and all maybe that's the
problem because you see why we won't
take that straight out alcoholic drink
guess what many of us have begun to
drink we've begun to drink that wine
that prophetic understanding that says
hey guys watch out for the Marxist
secular because they are going to take
away the rights of the PE and and
we wait a
minute wait a minute
as I read the great controversy I see
one chapter dedicated to the French
Revolution and in that chapter she
blames hypocritical Christianity for
what happened in the French
Revolution in the 22 chapters of the
Book of Revelation I see one chapter
dedicated to the Book of Revelation
every other chapter is dedicated to this
rise of this apostate power it's as if
God is saying no matter what but Lord
communism no no matter what but Islam No
matter what but Germany no matter what
no matter what threat you see
no my
people that I need you to keep your eye
focused on one thing because listen
y'all I don't how many of you
so I don't even remember the first time
I
drank and that ought to tell you
something yeah I didn't catch that
I don't remember the first time I drank
whatever I drank I was like maybe I can
handle this I don't remember
anything all it takes beloved is a sip
from the wine of
Babylon and before you know it you're
not thinking
straight you're not thinking
straight there are things 10 years ago
that I would have fre really been able
to say up here hey you know can't do
that these days you got to be
careful when you try to
preach the Three Angels
messages since when did listen y'all
before I came out here I was like Lord
please if there any stones in the pews
like let them not find
them like honestly I mean you know I
wasn't that nervous but I was just like
Lord please just help help help please
Jesus helped the people hear what I have
to say since
when have we had to become
careful about speaking about this second
beast of Bible
prophecy since when have we be had to
become careful within our own Circles of
pointing out what's happening in the
political
world to show prophecy being
fulfilled it has become so now that to
speak of what's open to openly speak of
what's happening in the political world
you're being political
Pastor
what you need to just keep keep keep to
the
Bible oh so don't identify the things
that are clearly happening before our
eyes that we have prophesied about for
over 15 don't talk about that just
keep just shut up and
dribble some of y'all caught that some
of y'all caught that
listen to this listen to this as the
storm approaches a large class who have
professed faith in the third Angel's
message but have not been Sanctified
through obedience to the truth abandon
their position and join the ranks of the
opposition now what I need y to
understand listen let me make you read
by uniting with the world and partaking
of its Spirit they have come to view
matters in nearly the same light and
when the test is brought they are
prepared to choose the easy and popular
side men of talent and pleasing address
who once rejoice in the truth employ
their powers to deceive and mislead
Souls they become the most bitterest
enemies of their Brethren I'm not going
to read any
further she's talking about administ
here joining the opposition they will
come to see things in the same light as
the opposition and because of that
they're going to join them now my
question to you is this who is the
opposition that she's speaking about
here
is the opposition the secular atheistic
Marx is that the opposition she's
talking about the oppos in the context
of the chapter in The Great controversy
the opposition she's talking about is a
poate
protestantism so what she's saying is
Adventists will begin to see things so
much in the same light as apostate
Protestants
and it might first start out with you
know talking to their brethen like no
don't talk about
that why why are you talk you should be
worried about that over there not this
right
here how in the world is it that
Adventists will get to the point where
they are so on the same page with these
Fallen
churches that when the test comes
they're already of The Same
Spirit I'm kind of diverting from my
notes here but I just got to tell you
something belov listen to me the wine of
the the wrath of Babylon the wine of the
wrath of
Babylon huh no the wine of the wrath of
Babylon does Babylon have
wrath so what is Babylon angry
at come on come on think with
me Babylon we are angry
what are they angry
with
worldliness the
Heathen the ungodly secular that's what
they're talking about today right look
at where our nation is
going now beloved what kind of Wrath is
this it's the same kind of Wrath that
the Pharisees had against the
Romans it's the same kind of Wrath that
they had against the woman caught in
adultery now remember I'm not talking
about people I'm talking about
systems and so this this this this far
this false
wrath they are the enemies right there
Adventist should be
like yeah but the Bible
says but instead what's happening is
we're getting caught up in that Spirit
of wrath y'all not feeling
me we're getting caught up in that same
Spirit of Wrath now I got to ask you was
Jesus wrathful with the
Romans he wasn't was he but but but the
leaders of the Jews certainly were the
Pharisees certainly were if you're
righteous you ought to be angry at those
Romans Jesus was like you don't y'all
don't even understand my
mission my mission is I came to save
Romans
I came to save the homosexual I came to
save the drag queen I Came To Save The
Atheist who is by the way atheist
because of your
example because of your failure to
represent my character
correctly so Adventist I don't need you
to be like fall in Babylon I want you to
stand apart your mission is to call my
people out of that confusion and also
call worldly people and atheists and
call all those people into my grace and
into the knowledge of the
truth that's what I need y'all to do as
Christian
nationalists but for many of us we're
getting caught
up we're getting caught up in that wine
we're getting caught up in that wrath
and that wrath is now turning on our own
brethren in the church
you don't know how many friends I have
lost over the last four five six
years for preaching the very same thing
I've been preaching since I came into
the
church nothing
changed go back and watch my videos from
10 years ago 15 years ago
prophetically first Beast second beast I
have not changed anything and
now yeah we're not listening to you
Pastor yo why you always picking on the
lamb I I don't understand it y'all but
now now I'm really going to ask a
question how many of you love
me cuz if y'all thought before like you
had to love me now you're going to have
to pray like Lord father father help me
to see see how what happened how did we
get to the place where we are right
now how have we gotten to this place
where where there is this split this
this this division within
adventism
so and 1777 George Washington mandates
small poox vaccine for all his
soldiers did Advent say anything about
this Adventist were
silent I'm just waiting for some of
y'all to catch what's going on here
you're like they sure were silent cuz
they weren't existing yes okay very good
very good
1809 Massachusetts institutes the first
vaccine mandate 183
Congress establishes the US vaccine
agency 1855 Massachusetts institutes the
first school of uh the first
school vaccine mandates 1867 the urban
Ohio Board of Health passes a law
requiring citizens to get available
vaccines in the event of future
epidemics 1902 Congress passes the
biological controls act 1905 the Supreme
Court decides Jacobson versus
Massachusetts uh which is again another
vaccine mandate showing that it was
constitutional 1922 the US Supreme Court
uh decides zuk versus King uh 1944 the
Supreme Court decides prince versus
Massachusetts all of these vaccines are
for the good of the general public 1977
the Nationwide child Nationwide child
immunization initiative begins 1980 all
50 states have laws
requiring vaccines for children to
attend public
schools where was the Adventist
outcry where was the the general
conference is trampling on our right the
where was it where was it hold on 1987
the Arizona court of appeals decides
Maricopa County Health Department V
Department V Haron to 2015 California
becomes the first state to eliminate
personal belief exemptions to vaccines
for children in public and private
schools okay and then comes
Co now I want you to know that I love
you
and your Christian duty is to love
me yeah that's right so what was
different with
co co was a religious
thing so
said the
Beast with the horns of a lamb that
spake as a
dragon
that's what they said they didn't get it
from
us do y'all catch what I'm saying they
didn't get it from us they started
saying
this see
that um the great re the Great Awakening
versus the great reset and there's a
little book there you maybe you can see
it on the screen it says covid-19 and
the great
reset in the
Evangelical Christian nationalist world
now when I say Christian nationalis what
am I talking about
now a counterfeit Christian
nationalism there's a genuine Christian
nationalism and there's a counterfeit
Christian nationalism and in the
counterfeit version of Christian
nationalism Co became a religious
talking point it became a point of
religious
liberty the same people who are going to
take away y' y'all
the same power that is going to take
away religious liberty said this is a
religious liberty issue and you know
what happened they started pushing this
and so
um now how many of you understand is
you're a Christian duty to
love you do understand that right you
know that God holds you accountable that
if you don't love me like y'all not
going to be
saved it's true and if I don't love you
I'm not going to be saved
so if we love each other let's just give
a nice raised hand in the air we love
each other like half of you just didn't
raise your hand just now you're like ah
nah nah n you gone too far
so the prophets of this
movement began to push a certain
narrative the elites want covid-19
lockdowns to usher in a great reset
anybody ever heard of the great reset
it's this listen to me y'all it's not a
great controversy idea it's not a Bible
idea it's the apostate Protestant
version of end time events there is
going to be a great reset where the
global Elites whoever they
are the secularists the marxists the
people who hate God and the Bible and
religion are coming to get you and
unless we stand firm against what they
are doing now it's going to only end in
more
trouble now hold on like I went back to
the great controversy and I was like the
great reset the great reset the great no
the great controversy the great
controversy the great controversy I
don't see a great reset here I don't see
anything about the secularists taking
over the world and and we having to
stand up again no all I see is the
second beast of Bible
prophecy trying to point a finger at
some other direction to say say that's
the
enemy and so not only did we find it
there um another well-known person they
are using covid to crash Western
economies and Implement communist
policies uh uh Biden's covid shutdown
globalist reset plans will
American freedoms and economy and so
what happened was instead of us watching
the news the Heaven's news because I
like news I love the news
and and and Heaven has a news
source so I love watching the news I
pull out the news
it I love watching the news the good
news the good news because the good news
is good because it tells us exactly
what's going to Happ us happen and it
and and it differentiates between good
news and fake
news and so what began happening was
that Adventist began following fake
news in the place of the good
news which says man I like this nation
better than this
nation I believe that what what's being
T and see here's what happens once you
start sipping up this wine I'm telling
you you don't think straight
anymore because once you sip a part of
the wine you you only all what happens
now is you just begin to drink more and
more one drink turns into two turns into
three and now you begin to hear things
like listen man the major threat that
admin us need to worry about now is
Marxism and
communism and there's a deep state
within the general
conference I'm telling you man watch out
for that and and you know that deep
State you see you start hearing deep
State deep State deep State and and and
and and this and and I'm telling you
you then get to the place where you hear
that Christian nationalism is just a
fantasy it's a phantom it's not real and
the Adventists that are talking about
the rise of Christian nationalism are
just there there there it's not in the
Bible and Ellen White never talked about
it
what what
planet what
universe and then you remember oh yeah
it's it's
wine it's one woe un the who has woe who
has sorrow who has contentions who has
babblings who has wounds without cause
who has redness of eyes they that tar
long at the wine they that go to seek
what mixed wine look not thou upon the
wine when it is red when it giveth its
color in the cup when it moveth itself a
right at the last it biteth like a
serpent and sth like an add Thine
Eyes come on
y'all Thine Eyes shall what
behold
strange
women
y' Thine Eyes Shall Behold strange women
and thine heart shall utter perverse
things you guys this thing is
real this thing is
serious
and so religious liberty be begins to
become
reconstructed this is what religious
liberty is I need y'all to understand
something the pilgrims had an idea of
religious
liberty their idea of religious liberty
was Liberty for us and everybody else
has to follow what we
want and that's why they put Roger
Williams out of the community cuz he was
like no no no no religious liberty for
everybody even if it's it's
uncomfortable for
us that's the kind of religious liberty
that the second beast of Bible prophecy
is talking about and many of us are not
adopting that version of religious
liberty and claiming things about
religious liberty that were not written
listen y'all read the chapter in The
Great controversy called the liberty of
conscience and you will see every time
she speaks about it when
protestantism shall take way the
right she never says when the government
when the secularist left when the evil
people no she says Protestant
America when they take away the rights
of worship and I thought to myself you
know what this is funny the very people
who are now and I'm talking about you
know within the Christian world the very
same people who are like it doesn't
matter what you put in your body you can
eat anything because God made all things
clean so it doesn't matter wine meat
uncleaned there's no it's not what goes
into the man that defiles the man but
what you remember all that how all of a
sudden Are You Now using this I don't
want to defile my temple
huh
really so the next time you like get
into some discussion with someone who's
like you know uh we can eat all kinds of
things you kind of know a route to
go is
hypocrisy and many of us fell for it now
I got
wow I got three minutes uh three minutes
left and I
just so let me do
this project
2025 where a group of
Protestants
evangelicals not I shouldn't say a
group think tanks conservative think
tanks from all across America come
together and write this 920 page
document about how they want to take
over if a republican wins how many of
you love
me and I love you back if a republican
wins this is what they want to do I'm
just going to skip some stuff here if a
republican wins this is what they want
to do
um they want to
dismantle parts of the US
government and replace it with something
else the center for renewing America is
preparing for the next Republican
Administration to govern
as Christian nationalists now y'all
y'all need to catch
this on page 589 of this document of
proposed changes Sabbath rest
God ordained the Sabbath as a day of
rest and until very recently the
judeo-christian tradition sought to
honor the Mandate by moral and legal
regulation of work on that day moreover
a shared day off makes it possible for
families and communities to enjoy time
off together rather than as atomized
individuals and provides a healthier
Cadence Cadence of life for everyone
unfortunately that communal day of rest
has eroded under the pressures of
consumerism and secularism especially
for lowincome workers so you know what
they want to do they want to implement a
Sunday
law now you would think we would be
blaring you would think Adventist would
be jumping up and down out
but
no so let me get this
straight the pope sneezes and we're like
Sunday
law Sunday law Sunday law
Sunday y'all understand that the Bible
and spirit of Prophecy let us know that
when a Sunday law happens it it doesn't
come from the
pope it comes from apostate
protestantism it it we're not supposedly
looking over in Europe at climate change
oh this we're supposed to be looking at
it here in America and right here in
America they've just said hey guys
Adventists Sunday law and we're
like the pope climate change secularism
guys Sunday law
[Laughter]
nope I'm not
looking didn't hear
it I got 20 seconds
left let's become Christian
nationalists biblical Christian
nationalists let's become nationalists
of the Kingdom of
Heaven let's be about our father's work
let's be about spreading this
gospel let's put down the
cup Jesus said in the parable where he
changed water into wine the man there
said wow you know people normally put
out the best wine first and then and
then uh you know bring the worst later
but here it is you save the best wine
for
last we got the best wine
y'all we have the best wine and God is
saving it for last let's get it out into
the
world heavenly father thank you for
speaking to
us Lord hard things were said today I
pray that for those who need to hear it
that their hearts would be
receptive Lord I pray that you would
make us true Christian nationalists
nationalists of the kingdom of heaven
and remind us Lord of our mission may we
stay focused and not be distracted by
the devil's
rabbits please Lord forgive us for
taking our eye off of our ancient
prophetic message and may we redeem the
time is our prayer in Jesus name
amen